Tyrone Justin R. Sta. Maria

Email: tyrone.stamaria35@gmail.com Linkedin: Tyrone Sta. Maria Github: TyroneGithub Website: https://tyronegithub.github.io/

Summary

I am an undergraduate student taking up a Bachelor of Science in Computer Science at De La Salle University. Outside my regular duties as a student I participate in organizations and communities where I work on different projects that involve both research and software development. I am willing to expand my knowledge and skills by working on different projects.

Education	
De La Salle University, Manila Bachelor of Science in Computer Science with Specialization in Software Technology	2019 - Present
Lourdes School Quezon City Senior High School (STEM)	2017 - 2019
Experience	
User Experience Philippines (UXPH) Web developer / Researcher / Volunteer	2020 - Present
La Salle Computer Society (LSCS) Associate Vice President for Research and Development	2020 - Present
Skills	
Prototyping: Figma Software Development: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Hugo, Gatsby, Jekyll, Pyt	hon, MySQL
Projects	
UXPH 2020 Website http://uxph.org/	2020
DLSU Annual Recruitment Week 2020 https://arw.dlsu-cso.org/	2020
ACM SigCHI Manila Chapter Website https://sigchimnl.org/	2020

2019

Online LLEAP Evaluation System http://lsqc.edu.ph/lleapevaluation/